[
  {
    "subject": "Mathametics",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
        "answers": ["1", "3", "4", "none of these"],
        "answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 2 / 2?",
        "answers": ["0", "4", "3", "1"],
        "answer": "1"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is five times eight?",
        "answers": ["40", "45", "50", "35"],
        "answer": "40"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 10%2?",
        "answers": ["0", "1", "both a and b", "none of these"],
        "answer": "0"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 5 - 35?",
        "answers": ["30", "-30", "both a and b", "none of these"],
        "answer": "-30"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Science",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Speed of light is ____",
        "answers": ["299....m/s", "399....m/s", "499....m/s", "none of these"],
        "answer": "299....m/s"
      },
      {
        "question": "Human body have ___ bones",
        "answers": ["204", "205", "206", "207"],
        "answer": "206"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Javascript",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Javascript is a ______ language",
        "answers": ["Programming", "Scripting", "both a and b", "Markup"],
        "answer": "both a and b"
      },
      {
        "question": "Javascript is introduced in _____",
        "answers": ["1994", "1995", "1996", "1997"],
        "answer": "1995"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which release of javascript have a major impact",
        "answers": ["es5", "es6", "es7", "es8"],
        "answer": "es6"
      },
      {
        "question": "Javascript can be used outside of a browser?",
        "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which one is a high order function",
        "answers": ["forEach()", "map()", "reduce()", "All of these"],
        "answer": "All of these"
      },
      {
        "question": "Strings are immutabe",
        "answers": ["Yes", "No"],
        "answer": "Yes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Node.js can be run on?",
        "answers": ["Windows", "Unix", "Linux", "All of these"],
        "answer": "All of these"
      },
      {
        "question": "The syntax for spead operator is?",
        "answers": ["...array", "[...array]", "{...obj}", "All of these"],
        "answer": "All of these"
      },
      {
        "question": "The rest operator is used for?",
        "answers": [
          "Change variable type",
          "collect data",
          "collect arguments of function",
          "collect arguments of object"
        ],
        "answer": "collect arguments of function"
      },
      {
        "question": "Nesting of callbacks is called",
        "answers": [
          "Callback nesting",
          "Callback hell",
          "Callback Bundle",
          "Callback Complexity"
        ],
        "answer": "Callback hell"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "React.js",
    "questions": [
      { "questions": "", "answers": ["", "", "", "", ""], "answer": "" },
      { "questions": "", "answers": ["", "", "", "", ""], "answer": "" },
      { "questions": "", "answers": ["", "", "", "", ""], "answer": "" },
      { "questions": "", "answers": ["", "", "", "", ""], "answer": "" },
      { "questions": "", "answers": ["", "", "", "", ""], "answer": "" }
    ]
  }
]
